Lewis Farut Noguera Gómez

UI Designer and Frontend Developer | React-Native Developer

Email: Lewisnoguera@gmail.com

Tel: (+57) 320 797 1953

Github: https://github.com/LewisFNoguera
Portfolio: https://lewisnoguera.netlifv.app

| About me

I am a FrontEnd developer and UI-oriented graphic designer, with more than 5 years of experience implementing UI, as well as in the area of interactivity and functionality. I have skills in HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript web development using different frameworks and libraries: Angular, ReactJS or VueJs, and in the implementation of user interfaces for mobile apps through frameworks like SenchTouch and ReactNative. I have also worked as a UI designer creating prototypes and wireframes in Figma and AdobeXD. Enthusiastic and passionate about new technologies; always open-minded to learn new things.

| Experience

Monetta

Position: Frontend Developer | React-Native Developer

October 2021 - At Present

Design and development of modules and reusable components for the main app in **React-Native**. Design and development of modules and components for the product's administrative CMS in **React** and **Tailwindcss**. Design and development of static web pages in **HTML**, **CSS** and **Javascript**. Design of components in **Figma** . Support in the improvement or creation of **backend** services using **NestJS**.

Cetoco

Position: Frontend Developer | React-Native Developer | UI Designer

October 2020 - October 2021

Creation of user interfaces for the Monetta app and for client companies such as OWO, Davivienda Bank (Maps) in **Figma** and **AdobeXD**. Front-End development through libraries or frameworks such as **React-Nativ**, **React**, **Angular** and **TailwindCSS** for administrative **CMS** and websites, implementing agile methodologies such as **SCRUM** and using tools such as **BITBUCKET** and **JIRA** for the management of the development team and achievement of objectives.



Adatec

Position: UI Designer | Frontend Developer

August 2015 - September 2020

Design of graphical user interfaces for cell phones and websites, UI implementation in React and Sencha Touch. Design and development of business websites such as product page and homepage based on Wordpress. Generation of graphic pieces for social networks, design and development of pieces for Mailchimp. Modification and use of ticketing tools such as OSTicket.

| Skills

Operating systems: MacOS

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Html/CSS

Frameworks / Librerías: React, Vue, Angular, Astro, React Native

CSS:: Sass, TailwindCss, TailwindUI

Design: Figma, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, Adobe Acrobat

Tools: SCRUM, Postman, GitHub, Styled Component.

| Education

Professional Drawing Academy Foundation | Cali (2015 - 2018)

Graphic Designer

University of Las Palmas de Gran Canaria | España (2012 - 2015: Not completed)

Computer Engineering

CIFP Villa de Agüimes | España (2010 - 2012)

Superior Degree in Computer Applications Development

| Online Certifications

- Dart: From zero to Expert | (Devtalles)
- Vuejs: From zero to Expert | (Devtalles)
- Vuejs: Intermediate | (Devtalles)
- Typescript | (Udemy)

| Languages

Spanish (Native)

English (Basic)

